

FREYZA FACHRURROZI KUSUMA

Full-Stack Developer

CONTACT



+62 812 1233 2042



freyzafk08@gmail.com



Jalan Bacang No. 33, Lubang Buaya, Cipayung, East Jakarta, Greater Jakarta, Indonesia, 13810

EDUCATION

Mercu Buana University | (2020 - 2024) **Bachelor of Computer Science**

With specialization in Data Science and Software Development

51 Jakarta Vocational High School | (2016 - 2019) Senior High School

SKILLS

- ✓ Front-End Programming Language (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, JQuery, SASS)
- ✓ Back-End Programming Language (PHP, JavaScript, Python)
- ✓ Framework (Laravel, Codeigniter, Next JS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS)
- ✓ Mobile Programming Language (Java)
- ✓ Database Management (Microsoft SQL) Server, MySQL, MySQL Workbench, and Postgre SQL)
- ✓ Web Design and Mockup (Figma)
- ✓ Version Control Management (Github)
- ✓ REST API Understanding

OTHER SKILLS

- Algorithm & Data Structure
- Using other tools (Postman and ChatGPT)
- Al & Machine Learning

LANGUAGE

- Indonesian (Native)
- English (Upper Intermediate)
- Japanese (Basic)

PROFILE

A self-motivated and curious person with four years of experience working with front-end and back-end web development. Able to build complex and simple websites and apps with various tools, programming languages, frameworks, and databases. Enthusiast in web and mobile application development, AI, and data science. Willing to learn new understanding and skills related to technology.

EXPERIENCE

Computer Network Services | (Apr 2023 - Present) Senior IT Developer

Port-Vila, Vanuatu (Remote)

- Preserve both clients and company systems using various technologies.
- Assist in figuring out several problems related to web development and database management system.
- Test and debug several web systems.
- Manage many databases.

Akses Prima Indonesia | (Dec 2022 - Apr 2023) Full-Stack Developer

Jakarta, Indonesia (On-Site)

- Evolved simple or complex systems based on clients' needs.
- · Participated in plenty of meetings alongside clients to discuss a project and agreement.
- Did daily maintenance of clients' web systems.
- Tested and debugged several web systems in development and production.

IFCA Software Indonesia | (Nov 2019 - Dec 2022) **Software Consultant**

Jakarta, Indonesia (On-Site)

- Implemented IFCA ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) System.
- Assisted in training users how to use the system.
- Suggested and provided a lot of solutions to users in need as they directly dealt with IFCA Application System.
- Fixed their data if there were a bunch of anomaly data because of the system.
- Attended many meetings along with users to discuss many cases and problems in IFCA Application System.